Hey, first of all, congratulations on,
you know, getting drafted and coming to
Las Vegas. My first question is just
just talk about Could you talk about a
little bit about your skill set and what
do you feel like you you would be
provided at the next level?
I mean, I just think I'm a great run
stopper. Um,
great hands, great strong at the point
of attack and uh play with a
uh tenacity that is, you know, at a
extremely high level.
When you look at the Raiders defensive
line, how excited are you get to work
with some of the players that maybe
you've seen over the years like Max
Crosby?
Yeah, Max Crosby, great and there's, you
know, plenty of other great D-linemen
there, uh great coaching staff. I just
can't wait to get down there and get to
work.
Uh
I had two questions for you. One, how
much did you communicate with the
Raiders in the process and were they on
your radar in terms of teams that might
be picking you?
Yeah, the Raiders the Raiders were
definitely in the process. Um, I met
with the D-line coach um on Zoom and,
you know, had good talks with the um
scouts and stuff. So, I knew they were
it was definitely going to film and come
and get me. So, I'm really excited and
really happy.
My other question was um I know you were
a a really good baseball player, too,
and uh you had the opportunity to play
that uh collegiately. Uh how much
thought was given to that and I mean, I
guess now you're a pretty happy with the
decision that you made?
Yeah, I'm 300-something plus pounds, so
I think I made the right decision to
play football and not baseball.
What would you say is one of the biggest
uh qualities that you would bring to the
locker room and the strengths that you
bring to this team?
Yeah, I think I'm just uh I just care
for the guys in the locker room. Um, I'm
going to get there. I'm a new guy, but,
you know, I'm going to love everybody
and care for everybody in the locker
room and I think that's the most
important thing and that's I think
that's the best thing I bring to the
table just being a good person and
caring about everybody.
Hey Brandon, um I was reading your bio.
It said you put on nearly 50 lb when you
rolled at NC State. So, like you slid
around the defensive line. I'm just
curious your experience playing, you
know, multiple positions along the
D-line there.
Yeah, I played freaking every every
position on the D-line and um
I think I found what I'm best at, which
is nose tackle and um
you know, I'm just ready to get after
and get to Las Vegas.
I think that looks like it. Thanks so
much, Brandon. We appreciate your time.
Thank you all. Nice to meet you all.
Have a good one.